Trice, Harrison M. Additional Papers /4164
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Treatment Centers - Horizon Hospital, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Toward a Theory of Turnover, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- The Correlates of Turnover, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Introduction to the Study of Turnover, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- The Effects of Turnover on Organization, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- The Theories of Turnover, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Extending Workplace Democracy - Recent Employee Unions, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Union Responses to Alcoholism, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 40)
- Power Dependencies and the Distribution of Influence in Universities, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 41)
- Perspectives on Urban Community Development and Community Organization, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 42)
- Values in Action - the Meaning of Executive Vignettes, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 43)
- Thoughts on Personal and Vocational Rehabilitation for Disabilities due to Alcoholism, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 44)
- The Alcoholism Problem as a Cultural Question, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 45)
- Proposals for Wellness Programs, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 46)
- Women and Alcoholism, 1966-1980 (Box 10, Folder 47)
- The Hidden Alcoholism Problem Among Employed Women, 1958-1979 (Box 10, Folder 48)
- Trends Among Women Alcoholism, 1970-1982 (Box 10, Folder 49)
- A Review and Assessment of Trends in Female Crime, 1965-1976, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Employment Experience of Women in Non-Traditional Occupations, 1964-1981 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- The Female Entrepreneur, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Sexual Equality and Female Labor Force Participation, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Housewives and Their Work - 1957 and 1976, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Women and Alcohol - Intoxication, Metabolism, and the Menstrual Cycle, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- The Significant of Social Support During Stressful Life Events, 1972-1981 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- Sex Roles and Drug Abuse, 1973-1979 (Box 10, Folder 57)
- Women and Suicide, 1974-1980 (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Feminism and Union Participation, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 59)
- On Good Works and Good Work, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Work, Personality, and Happiness, 1968-1981 (Box 10, Folder 61)
- Work and Familial Wellbeing, 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 62)
- Work Motivation, 1973-1980 (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Women and Drugs, 1970-1978 (Box 10.1, Folder 1)
- Cohen, Sidney, and Blutt, Mitchell - Hypnotic Drug Therapy, 1978 (Box 10.1, Folder 2)
- Prather - Drug Usage as an Index of Stress among Women I and II, 1975-1977 (Box 10.1, Folder 3)
- Riemer, J. - Making a Trade - Women Apprentices in the Building Construction Industry (Box 10.1, Folder 4)
- Brinkerhoff, M. - Women who want to work in a man's world, 1977 (Box 10.1, Folder 5)
- Blitz, R. - Women in the Professions, 1870-1970, 1974 (Box 10.1, Folder 6)
- Robin, S. - The Female in Engineering, 1969 (Box 10.1, Folder 7)
- Patterson, S. and Engelberg, L. - Women in Male-Dominated Professions, 1978 (Box 10.1, Folder 8)
- Riemer, J. and Bridwell, L. - How Women Survive in Non-Traditional Occupations (Box 10.1, Folder 9)
- Winslow - Married Women in Industry, 1923 (Box 10.1, Folder 10)
- Western Electric Policy (Box 10.1, Folder 11)
- Bypass - Of Policy and Program, 1972-1975 (Box 10.1, Folder 12)
- Western Electric Policy Books (Box 10.1, Folder 13)
- Supervisory Role in Occupational Alcoholism Programs, 1979 (Box 10.1, Folder 14)
- Drug and Alcohol Use in Universities, 1977 (Box 10.1, Folder 15)
- Alcoholism Among Different Careers, 1977 (Box 10.1, Folder 16)
- Women and Alcoholism, 1979 (Box 10.1, Folder 17)
- Above and Beyond Drug Testing - Using Pre-Performance Tests as an Alternative for Enhancing Work Place Safety (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Above and Beyond Drug Testing - Using Pre-Performance Tests as an Alternative for Enhancing Work Place Safety (Duplicate) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Copy of the article in folder 1
- Absenteeism Among High Status and Low Status Problem Drinkers, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Adaptation to Inadequate Role Assignments (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Adaptation to Occupational Role Change (Box 11, Folder 5)
- The Affiliation Motive and Readiness to Join Alcoholics Anonymous, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Alateen, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- The Aging Collegian - Drinking Pathologies Among Executive and Professional Alumni, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Al-Anon, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Alcohol Abuse and Work Organizations, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Alcohol Abuse and Work Organizations (Duplicate), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Copy of the article in folder 10
- Alcohol Abuse and Work Organizations (Second Duplicate), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  Copy of the article in both folder 10 and folder 11
- Alcohol and Crime, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Alcohol and Drugs in the Workplace, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Alcohol, Illegal Drugs, and the Work World - The Need for a Comparative Perspective, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Alcohol and Drugs in the Workplace - Costs, Controls, and Controversies, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Alcohol and Mental Health Programs in the Workplace, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Alcohol and Mental Health Programs in the Workplace (Duplicate), 1990 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  Copy of the article in folder 17
- Alcoholic Employees, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- The Alcoholic Employee and His Supervisor - A General Management Problem, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- The Alcoholic Executive (Box 11, Folder 21)
- The Alcoholic and His Shop Steward, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- The Alcoholic and His Supervisor, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Alcoholics Anonymous, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- AA and EAP - The Historical Link, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Alcoholism in America - Revisited, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Alcoholism in America - Revisited (Published Version), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  Published version of the article in folder 26
- Alcoholism - Group Factors in Etiology and Therapy, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- The Alcoholism Coordinator - Achilles Heel of the Federal Program, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- The Alcoholism Coordinator - Achilles Heel of the Federal Program (Duplicate), 1976 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  Copy of the article in folder 29
- Alcoholism in Industry, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Alcoholism Programs in Unionized Work Settings - Problems and Prospects in Union-Management Cooperation, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Alcoholism Programs in Unionized Work Settings - Problems and Prospects in Union-Management Cooperation (Duplicate) (Box 11, Folder 33)
  Copy of the article in folder 32
- Alcoholism and the Employee, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Alcoholism and the Employee (Duplicate), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  Copy of the article in folder 34
- Alcoholism and the Employee (Second Duplicate), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  Copy of the articles in both folder 34 and folder 35
- Alcoholism and the Worker, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Alcoholism and the Work World - Prevention in a New Light, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- Alcoholism and the Work World - Prevention in a New Light (Duplicate), 1970 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  Draft copy of the article in folder 38
- An Anthropological View of Conflict in Work Organizations, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- An Anthropological View of Conflict in Work Organizations (Duplicate), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  Copy of the article in folder 40
- Applied Research Studies - Job-Based Alcoholism and EAPs, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Applied Research Studies - Job-Based Alcoholism and EAPs (Draft Version), 1979 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  Draft copy of the article in folder 42
- Applied Research Studies - Job-Based Alcoholism and EAPs (Duplicate), 1980 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  Copy of the article in folder 42
- Arbitration of Medical Malpractice Suits (Box 11, Folder 45)
- Assessing Personal, Role, and Organizational Predictors of Managerial Commitment, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 46)
- Assessing Personal, Role, and Organizational Predictors of Managerial Commitment (Duplicate), 1978 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  Copy of the article in folder 46
- An Assessment of Alcoholism Counseling Programs Within the AFL-CIO (Box 11, Folder 48)
- The Assessment of Change - A Look into Pandora's Box (Box 11, Folder 49)
- The Assessment of Change in Training and Therapy (Box 11, Folder 50)
- The Assessment of Change in Training and Therapy (Duplicate) (Box 11, Folder 51)
  Copy of the article in folder 50
- Becoming an EAP Worker (Box 11, Folder 52)
- Becoming an EAP Worker (Duplicate) (Box 11, Folder 53)
- The Best-Worst Technique for Measuring Work Performance in Organizational Research, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 54)
- The Best-Worst Technique for Measuring Work Performance in Organizational Research (Published Version), 1984 (Box 11, Folder 55)
  Published version of the article in folder 54
- The Billion Dollar Hangover (Box 11, Folder 56)
- Broad Brush and Employee Alcoholism Programs, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 57)
- Broad Brush and Employee Alcoholism Programs (Duplicate), 1973 (Box 11, Folder 58)
  Copy of the article in folder 57
- Broad Brush and Employee Alcoholism Programs - Pro and Con, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 59)
- The Ceremonial Effect - Manifest Function or Latent Dysfunction in the Dynamic Organization, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 60)
- The Ceremonial Effect - Manifest Function or Latent Dysfunction in the Dynamic Organization (Duplicate), 1983 (Box 11, Folder 61)
  Copy of the article in folder 60
- Change and Mental Health - The Industrial Case, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 62)
- Charisma and Its Routinization in Two Social Movement Organizations, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 63)
- Charisma and Its Routinization in Two Social Movement Organizations (Duplicate), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  Copy of the article in folder 63
- Charisma and Its Routinization in Two Social Movement Organizations (Second Duplicate), 1986 (Box 11, Folder 65)
  Copy of the article in both folder 63 and folder 65
- Clinical and Nonclinical Programs in the Work Place, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Cocaine Anonymous, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Comments and Discussion (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Comments and Discussion (Published Version), 1991 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  Published version of article in folder 68
- Commonalities and Differences in Occupational Programs (Box 11, Folder 70)
- Communication of Power Relations in Organizations Through Cultural Rites, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 71)
- Communication of Power Relations in Organizations Through Cultural Rites (Duplicate), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 72)
  Copy of the article in folder 71
- Communication of Power Relations in Organizations Through Cultural Rites (Second Duplicate), 1988 (Box 11, Folder 73)
  Copy of the article in both folder 71 and folder 72
- Comparative Characteristics of Schizophrenics with Labels of Differing Intensity (Box 11, Folder 74)
- Contrasting Employee Assistance, Health Promotion, and Quality of Worklife Programs and Their Effects on Alcohol Abuse and Dependence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 75)
- Constructive Confrontation, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 76)
- Constructive Confrontation and Counseling, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 77)
- Constructive Confrontation and Other Referral Processes, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 78)
- Contributions of AA to Employee Assistance Programs (EAPs), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Contributions of AA to EAPs (Duplicate), 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- The Crucial Balance - Strategies for EAPs, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cultural Diversity - Subcultures and Countercultures in Work Organizations, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Cultural Diversity - Subcultures and Countercultures in Work Organizations (Duplicate), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Copy of the article in folder 4
- Cultural Diversity - Subcultures and Countercultures in Work Organizations (Second Duplicate), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Copy of the article in both folder 4 and folder 5
- Cultural Leadership in Organizations, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Cultural Leadership in Organizations (Duplicate), 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  Copy of the article in folder 7
- Cultures in Complex Organizations, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Current and Prospective Roles for Linking Organizational Researchers and Users, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Current and Prospective Roles for Linking Organizational Researchers and Users (Manuscript), 1983-1988 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  Manuscript copy of the article in folder 10
- Current and Prospective Roles for Linking Organizational Researchers and Users (Duplicate), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Data-Based Examination of the Selection Bias in the Evaluation of a Job-Based Alcoholism Program, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Data Based Research, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Definitions - Types of Risk Concept (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Definitions - Types of Risk Concept continued (Box 12, Folder 16)
  A continuation of the loose and handwritten papers found in folder 15
- Delabeling, Relabeling, and Alcoholics Anonymous, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Design and Implementation of Job-Based Alcoholism Programs, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Design and Implementation of Job-Based Alcoholism Programs (Published Version), 1982 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  Published version of the article in folder 18
- Developed Occupations, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Development of Deviant Drinking Behavior, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Deviance and Work, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Deviance and Work (Duplicate), 1972 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  Copy of the article in folder 22
- Deviance in the Workplace, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Deviance in the Workplace (Duplicate), 1989 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  Copy of the article in folder 24
- Differential Social Support Among US University Students for the Use of Various Drugs, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Differential Social Support Among US University Students for the Use of Various Drugs (Duplicate), 1973 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  Copy of the article in folder 26
- Differential Use of an Alcoholism Policy in Federal Organizations by Skill Level of Employees, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Differential Use of an Alcoholism Policy in Federal Organizations by Skill Level of Employees (Duplicate), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  Copy of the article in folder 28
- Differential Use of an Alcoholism Policy in Federal Organizations by Skill Level of Employees (Second Duplicate), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  Copy of the article in both folder 28 and folder 29
- Dilemmas of Evaluation in Community Mental Health Organizations, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Dilemmas of Evaluation in Community Mental Health Organizations (Duplicate), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  Copy of the article in folder 31
- Dilemmas of Evaluation in Community Mental Health Organizations (Second Duplicate), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  Copy of the article in both folder 31 and folder 32
- Drinking Behavior and Risk Factors Related to the Work Place, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Drug Testing in the Transportation Industry - The Maritime Case (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Drug Use in Industry, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 36)
- Drugs, Drug Abuse, and the Workplace, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 37)
- Drugs, Drug Abuse, and the Workplace (Duplicate), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  Copy of the article in folder 37
- Early Detection, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 39)
- Early Detection continued (Box 12, Folder 40)
  A continuation of the loose and handwritten papers in folder 39
- Evaluating the EAP Professional, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 41)
- Effective Hiring in Small Business Organizations, 1962-1964 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  First and second printing of the bulletin
- Effective Hiring in Small Business Organizations (Duplicate), 1964 (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Emotional Health and Employer Responsibility, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 44)
- Empirical Study of Howard Becker's Side-Bet Theory, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Employee Assistance and Drug Testing - Fairness and Injustice in the Workplace (Box 12, Folder 46)
- Employee Assistance Programs - Trice Lecture, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 47)
- Employee Assistance Programs - Blending Performance-Oriented and Humanitarian Ideologies to Assist Emotionally Disturbed Employees, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 48)
- Employee Assistance Programs - Blending Performance-Oriented and Humanitarian Ideologies to Assist Emotionally Disturbed Employees (Duplicate), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  Copy of the article in folder 48
- Employee Assistance Programs - Blending Performance-Oriented and Humanitarian Ideologies to Assist Emotionally Disturbed Employees (Second Duplicate), 1984 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  Copy of the article in both folder 48 and folder 49
- Employee Assistance Programs and Drug Testing (Box 12, Folder 51)
  Copy of the article in folder46
- Employee Assistance Programs Implications for Smoking Cessation Programs (Box 12, Folder 52)
- Employee Assistance Programs - Research at Cornell, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Employee Assistance Programs - Where do we stand in 1983? (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Employee Assistance Programs - The Whys and Hows, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Employee Attitudes toward Performance Appraisal, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- The Employed Alcoholic, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Encouraging Abstinence among Students - A National Approach to Primary Prevention of Alcoholism, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Evaluating Implementation of a Job-Based Alcoholism Policy, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Evaluating the Effectiveness of Interventions, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Evaluating the Effectiveness of Interventions - First Draft, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Evaluation of Alcoholics Anonymous, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Evaluation of Consultants and Coordinators, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Evaluation of the Corporate Headquarters Alcoholism Project, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Evaluation of the Corporate Headquarters Alcoholism Project (Duplicate), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  Copy of the article in folder 12
- Evaluation of New York State Occupational Alcoholism Program Consultant Network, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Evaluation of New York State Occupational Alcoholism Program Consultant Network (Duplicate), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  Copy of the article in folder 14
- Evaluation of New York State Occupational Alcoholism Program Consultant Network (Second Duplicate), 1977 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  Copy of the article in both folder 14 and folder 15
- An Evaluation of Program Evaluations, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Evaluation of Training, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Evaluation of Training (Manuscript), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  Manuscript copy of article in folder 18
- Exploring the Black Box, 1982 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Exploring the Black Box (Published Version), 1983 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  Published version of article in folder 20
- Factors Associated with Policy Implementation, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Federal Unions - Interorganizational Pressures Toward Conformity with Personnel Policies (Box 13, Folder 23)
- The Field Format, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Field Study of the Use and Perceived Effects of Discipline in Controlling Work Performance, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Field Study of the Use and Perceived Effects of Discipline in Controlling Work Performance (Duplicate), 1984 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Copy of the article in folder 25
- Formal Testimony Before Manpower and Housing Subcommittee, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Formal Testimony Before the Manpower and Housing Subcommittee (Duplicate), 1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  Copy of the article in folder 27
- Help Seeking and Helping Processes Within the Workplace- Assisting Alcoholic and other Troubled Employees, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- History of Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - 1900-1955, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- History of Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - 1955-1972, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- History of Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - 1955-1972 (Duplicate), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- How an Organization's Rites Reveal Its Culture, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- How to get a loved one into treatment for alcoholism, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Humanitarianism as well as the cost of the Alcoholic Program, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Humanitarianism in the Workplace (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Identifying and Confronting the Alcoholic Employee - Role of the Industrial Nurse, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Identifying the Problem Drinker on the Job, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Ideologies, Values, and Decision Making in Organizations, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Ideologies, Values, and Decision Making in Organizations (Duplicate), 1981 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  Copy of the article in folder 39
- Ideology and Referral Categories in Employee Assistance Program Research, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Ideology and Referral Categories in Employee Assistance Program Research (Duplicate), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  Copy of the article in folder 41
- ILR Press, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Illinois Bell (Drug Abuse Paper), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 44)
- The Impact of Employee Unions Upon Supervisory Decisions in Alcohol/Drug Programs, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Impact of federal Sector Unions on Supervisors' Use of Personnel Policies, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 46)
- Impact of federal Sector Unions on Supervisors' Use of Personnel Policies (Duplicate), 1980 (Box 13, Folder 47)
- Implementing Change, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 48)
- Implications for Intervention, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 49)
- Incidence of the Emotionally Disturbed Within the Administrative Units of a Large Organizations, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 50)
- Indirect Social Effects and Organizational Behavior, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 51)
- Individual And Occupational Levels of Professionalism (Box 13, Folder 52)
- Individual and Occupational Levels of Professionalism (Duplicate) (Box 13, Folder 53)
  Copy of the article in folder 52
- Industry Will Assist the Judge, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 54)
- An Industrial-Labor Relations Specialist Looks at Therapy for Alcoholism (Speech) (Box 13, Folder 55)
- The Industrial Nurse and the Alcoholic Employee, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 56)
- Inside EAPs - View from the New York State Thruway, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 57)
- Inside and Outside Change Agents in Occupational Programming, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 58)
- Interaction of Differential Social Support and Use of Various Drugs, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  Includes some French language material
- Interaction of Differential Social Support and the Use of Various Drugs (Duplicate), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  Includes some French language material; copy of the articles in folder 59; see also the contents of box 12 folders 26 and 27 for duplicate copies
- JABS (Journal of Applied Behavioral Science), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 61)
- JABS (Duplicate), 1988 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  Copy of the journal in folder 61
- Job Absenteeism and Drinking Behavior, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 63)
- Job Behavior of Problem Drinkers, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 64)
- Job Behaviors and the Denial Syndrome, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 65)
- Job Placement of the Alcoholic Employee, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 66)
- Job-Based Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Programs and Women Employees (Box 13, Folder 67)
  Handwritten material
- Job-Based Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Programs and Women Employees (Typed Version) (Box 13, Folder 68)
- Job-Based Alcoholism and Drug Abuse Programs and Women Employees (Loose Papers) (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Job-Based Alcoholism and Employee Assistance Programs, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - Motivating Problem Drinkers to Rehabilitation, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - Motivating Problem Drinkers to Rehabilitation (Published Version), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Published version of the article in folder 2
- Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - Motivating Problem Drinkers to Rehabilitation (Duplicate), 1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Copy of the article in folder 3
- Job-Based Alcohol and Drug Abuse Programs - Recent Developments and Research, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - How and Why They Work, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Job-Based Alcoholism Programs - Underlying Concepts and Strategy, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Journal of Drug Issues - Part 1, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Journal of Drug Issues - Part 2, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 9)